let questions=[
	{
		numb:1,
		question:"A computer system is the integration of physical entities called hardware and non physical entities called ",
		answer:"Software",
		options:[
			"Software",
			" Hardware",
			"Firmware",
			"Liveware"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:2,
		question:"CPU reads and executes program instructions, performs calculations and ____",
		answer:"make decisions",
		options:[
			"make distribution",
			"make direction",
			"make diversion",
			"make decisions"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:3,
		question:"____ card is an input device stores data in a microprocessor embedded in the card.",
		answer:" Smart",
		options:[
			" Smart",
			"Sim",
			"Magnetic",
			"Laser"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:4,
		question:"____ are a storage medium from which data is read and to which it is written by lasers.",
		answer:" Optical disks",
		options:[
			" Optical drives",
			" Optical disks",
			"Optical data",
			"NONE"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:5,
		question:"The instructions and data are stored in the ___ so that the processor can directly fetch and execute them.",
		answer:"Main memory",
		options:[
			"Control unit",
			"Permanent memory",
			"CPU",
			"Main memory"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:6,
		question:"Tracing, of any input record or process, performed on a system, back to its original source, is a/an",
		answer:"Audit trial",
		options:[
			"Audit trial",
			"Conversion",
			"Report generation",
			"Batch processing"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:7,
		question:"Problem analysis is done during",
		answer:" Systems analysis phase",
		options:[
			"Before system test",
			"System design phase",
			" Systems analysis phase",
			"All of these"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:8,
		question:"A computer type, processor, and operating system define its",
		answer:"Speed",
		options:[
			"Speed",
			" Size",
			"Brand",
			"Platform"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:9,
		question:"Which type of storage is a hard disc?",
		answer:" Non-volatile",
		options:[
			" Non-volatile",
			"Temporary",
			"Volatile",
			"Non-permanent"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:10,
		question:"Which protocol has been standardized by the International Standards Organization?",
		answer:"ISO",
		options:[
			"ISO",
			"CALL",
			" ISAM ",
			"NONE"
		]
	},
];